♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Hey! Are you a big, fat bastard
who loves eating at
Outback Steakhouse,
but thinks the portions
are too small?
Well, good news, fatass,
'cause now there's
the Outback Steakhouse Extreme!
We don't have a Bloomin' Onion,
we have a Bloomin' Pumpkin!
You know what else we got?
Elephant steaks!
50-pound elephant steaks!
And why don't you wash it down
with 40 ounces of malt liquor
and ranch dressing,
you fat!
Outback Steakhouse Extreme!
Punish! Your! Toilet!
Aw, man,
I bet that's where
Crocodile Dundee
eats every night.
Everything in Australia
is so fancy.
Yeah, Australia's
a beautiful place.
The best thing
about going there
is you get to fly
over the Pacific Ocean.
The greatest ocean
of all time.
Tell me you're joking.
Everyone knows that,
pound for pound,
the Atlantic is
the best ocean.
"Pound for pound"?
What are you talking about?
You can't weigh the ocean.
Yeah, scientists can.
They're doing
it all the time.
Pick up a book.
You're an idiot!
I'm an idiot?
All anybody remembers
about your argument
is that you're
in a wheelchair!
Guys, guys...
Let's stop
escalatin'
and take the stairs
for a minute.
What?
What are you talking about?
I'm saying you both
are making good points.
But sometimes two rights
can make a wrong.
I just... I just like
the Pacific Ocean!
It's a good ocean.
And so is
the Atlantic.
Isn't this
a beautiful planet
you two friends live on?
I guess Cleveland's right.
I'm sorry I got
so hotheaded.
I'm sorry, too.
Here, let me turn
your foot back around.
It kind of got twisted up
in our scuffle there.
Wow, Cleveland.
You calmed them down
just by talking
with your mouth and
your pretty lips.
Oh, it's nothin'.
Just a little something
I learned volunteering
as a youth counselor
down at my church.
Pretty much
just boils down
to four or five
catchphrases.
Like what?
Well, there's the
"stop escalatin'" one.
There's
"What do you think it means?"
"Pray on it, stay on it."
One's just kind of like a noise:
Hmm... mmm?
That's amazing.
Hey, you're way too good
to be doing that for free.
Maybe you should
open up an office.
You know, finally
start chipping away
at some of that
horrendous debt you've got.
Yeah, Peter's right.
I mean, it's not like
you've found a job
since you moved
back here anyway.
You know, that's
a not-half-bad idea.
And if I charge
my first patient $117,000,
I'm right back in it.
Thanks for spotting
my potential, Peter!
Hey, no problem, buddy.
I'm pretty perceptive.
That's how I can
always tell which guys
in the Wrangler Jeans
commercials beat their wives.
All of 'em.
Go around the block again,
she's still out front.
We've gone around
six times.
Let's just talk to her.
Eh, you're right.
Rip it off quick,
like a Band-Aid.
Hey, Meg, you know
Mr. Quagmire, right? Bye!
Hey, what's
going on here?
Oh, I'm selling
my old Beanie Babies
to make money
for the prom.
That seems
optimistic.
But look, if you want
to make real money,
I could try to get you
a job at the airport.
They always need
new TSA screeners.
Really?
Wow, that'd be great!
Thanks, Mr. Quagmire.
And thanks for
taking the time.
Most people aren't
usually that nice to me.
Ugh, gross.
Mayor West, after working
with you for some time now,
I believe you are affecting
your weird behaviors.
You are doing
deliberately odd things
to mask dark,
maybe even criminal, activities.
You are 100% aware
of what you're doing.
I think you're
a dangerous sociopath.
Cleveland, let me
tell you something.
You're absolutely  right.
Well, time to put
on my spaghetti hat!
I just never feel happy.
I strive for these things,
and I get them,
but at the end of the day,
I still don't feel fulfilled.
Hmm.
This is a problem that
requires more tweed.
Is it possible you're not
letting yourself be happy?
Like you don't feel
like you're worth it?
No, that's not it.
Hmm.
Maybe your accomplishments
don't feel real
because your brother
isn't here to see them.
Maybe...
That doesn't feel
quite right, either.
Hmm.
You don't want to
outshine your father.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Whew.
I was damn near out of tweed.
Okay, now, see?
She didn't say
"good morning" to me,
so I put an orange dot
on her boarding pass,
which means they're going
to search her anus.
I noticed you
also circled
a bunch of things
on her ticket.
Why did you
do that?
Because otherwise,
the line moves too quickly.
You see, the whole thing
we're going for here at the TSA
is a sort of bored fascism.
Huh.
I think I can handle that.
I did not tell
you to approach!
Great job!
The worst thing
a passenger can do
is approach your podium
before you tell them to.
As bad as those
19 hijackers were,
the people we see here
every day are much worse.
Boy, Larry, there's
a lot to remember.
I... I hope I don't
screw something up.
Trust me, you have
nothing to worry about.
You're basically
un-fireable.
What do you mean?
Come on, Meg.
Look around.
You're the hottest
person who works here.
Oh, wow.
Now that you mention it,
everybody does look
kind of dumpy.
That's not entirely
their fault.
They're all told to wear
a pair of their dads' pants.
Oh, speaking of
which, tomorrow,
bring in a pair of
your dad's pants.
Peter, you promised me
you would do the dishes.
Well, I was doing
the dishes for a while,
but they were
inexperienced,
so I ended up having
to rub one out.
Where in the hell did
you get the idea that
that's what I meant by
"doing the dishes"?
From Dirty Amelia Bedelia.
Almost done vacuuming the rug!
Dammit, Peter!
You're making me crazy!
Well, you know what?
Sounds like you need
some counseling.
Maybe you should go
talk to Cleveland.
Cleveland?
Why would I talk to Cleveland?
He's a therapist now,
and he's really great at helping
people with their problems.
Oh, I see.
You want me to tell
your best friend
my complaints about you
so he can back you up.
The new maid is peeing on me!
And she didn't even say
anything clever about it!
Look, you're the one who said
you were going crazy.
Just talk to him.
He's all about
helping people get well.
Just like Doc Martens.
So, how are you feeling today?
Terrible.
I've got blurry vision.
I feel cold and clammy.
And the nurse told me
there's blood in my stool.
Have you tried
wearing a lesbian shoe?
What?
Put this man down for
a pair of lesbian shoes.
Huh.
High fever, weight loss,
and extreme
respiratory difficulty.
Let's have this man intubated
and fit with a pair
of lesbian shoes.
Hi.
Are you the next
crazy person?
Um, I guess so.
I've been pretty depressed
since my wife died.
I'm sorry, I'm tryin' to read
the Costco Connection here.
There they are!
All right, since
you're a patient,
we're gonna talk about you
like you're not here.
You get all of her
squawkin' out, Doc?
Oh, I think we got to
the root of the problem.
Didn't we, Lois?
Absolutely.
All right, let's
dope her up good.
Turn that mouth off.
No, Peter, the problem is you.
What?
What the hell are you doing?
You're supposed to be my friend.
Dr. Brown,
I just killed nine people!
Uh, I mean,
I have ducks
on my feet.
Old, crazy harmless mayor.
Quack quack!
How can Cleveland say
I'm the problem?
All I do is sit
in the bathroom
and play on my phone.
Swipe... wipe...
swipe... wipe...
wipe... swipe...
Uh-oh.
That's a perfect example.
You put no effort
into this marriage.
Cleveland helped me see
that our entire relationship
has been you doing
whatever you want
and me cleaning
up the mess.
By the way,
your Svengali
is out there spraying
birds with a hose.
Ha ha!
Now you're wet!
Peter, I've had enough.
Cleveland and I think
we need to make some changes.
Oh, come on.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
You're gonna start helping
around the house,
and we're gonna start
doing things together.
We do stuff together.
Just last night,
I made you keep track
of all the words I know.
"Shoehorn.orn."
"Engine."
"Football."
Did I say "shoehorn"?
Yes.
Okay.
"Shoehorns."
Peter, please...
I've got an early doctor's
appointment tomorrow.
Ooh! "Early."
"Doctor."
Put those on there, too.
Uh, should I also put
down "appointment"?
No, I don't know
what that means.
Oh, "means."
Wow, look at the new girl!
She's so hot!
Yeah, her breasts
and her stomach
are different parts
of her body!
I think she
looks weird.
How come she's not
shaped like a potato?
That's part of the
interview and everything.
Whoa, sorry, ma'am,
we can't let you
through security
because you're "da bomb."
Scott, you're not supposed
to make jokes like that!
Well, I am carrying
more than three
ounces of liquid.
Oh, that's so
Muhammad Hot-a.
You're playing a
dangerous game, Scott!
All right, Peter,
Cleveland says you should help
with the chores.
So today, we're gonna
do laundry together.
Okay.
How does this work?
Well, you put the wet clothes
in the dryer,
you close the door
and you wait.
Oh, it just went to 39 minutes!
So you... you
just stand here
and watch the
whole time?
Shh-shh-shh.
Ah, the green shirt
went by again!
If it goes around 30 times
in five minutes,
you get to have a Diet Coke!
All right, according
to Cleveland,
it's also healthy
for couples
to have shared
activities.
So since you
like golf,
I thought we could
play a round.
So-so what do I do,
just aim for the pond?
No, you're not supposed
to hit it into the water.
But you hit it
into the water.
I know I hit it
Why do they even have water
if you're not supposed
to hit it there?
Because it's fun!
We're having fun!
Rah!
Look, it went further
than your ball!
Hey, are you doing
anything on Friday?
No, I don't think so.
Why?
Well, I'm doing security
at the roller rink
if you want to come watch me.
Sure!
Great, I'll pick
you up at 4:30.
Sounds good.
All right, well,
I'm up at the podium.
Time to make marks
on pieces of paper
no one will
ever see again.
I thought we had
plans on Friday.
Marla, I think we should
just be ugly friends.
Dammit, Cleveland has
completely ruined my life.
He's got Lois making me
help around the house
and spend more
time with her.
My own wife!
I know what
you mean, Peter.
He said I've gotta be
more open and receptive
to what Bonnie wants
to do in the bedroom.
Thank God I can't feel
anything back there.
You know what?
Screw Cleveland.
He's gonna tell
my wife stuff,
I'm gonna tell his
wife a few things.
What are you
talking about?
Well, remember how Cleveland
banged that stripper
at his bachelor party?
Oh, yeah!
And we were all
throwing bread at 'em?
Yeah.
Maybe I could tell
Donna about that.
Or... remember when Cleveland
wore briefs under his boxers
and we found out
and he told us not
to say anything?
Maybe we tell her that.
Uh, I think Peter's is better.
Okay, but we'll
keep mine ready.
Could be the nail
in the coffin.
Hey, fellas.
Cleveland, it ain't cool
what you've been telling Lois.
All right?
You're completely
messing things up for me.
And you gotta tell her
you were wrong
and put things back
the way they were.
I'm sorry it's
hard for you, Peter,
but personal growth
isn't always easy.
Look, if you don't
change what you're saying,
we're gonna tell Donna
you slept with that stripper
at your bachelor party.
Ah! Ah!
What are you doing?
I'm gonna play
"Locomotive Breath"
by Jethro Tull
while he runs.
Why the hell would you do
something stupid like that?
Careful, Peter,
or you're gonna lose
two friends today.
We now return
to Major League Baseball
with one distractingly ugly guy
behind home plate.
It's two to two
in the bottom of the sixth,
and I just can't get my eyes
off that man with the tall head.
It's quite a game, but man,
that guy is ugly.
I'll say, Gary.
What's the count?
No idea, Bill.
But you know, that guy
hasn't blinked this entire game.
Just a dead-eyed idiot
out on a Thursday afternoon.
Yup.
And the longer I watch him,
the more I wonder
if he's there by himself.
I think you're
on to something there.
That seat next to him's
been empty for hours.
Right you are, Gary.
I'm gonna see if
I can hit him with my apple.
Ah. Kind of short-armed it.
Oh, I'll get to
the bottom of this.
Take care, Donna.
Cleveland didn't show up to
my therapy session earlier,
and Donna says she hasn't
seen him for two days.
Interesting.
She also weirdly told me
that she squatted 250 today.
I'm not even sure
if that's good.
It's scary good.
Well, I am off
to try and get out
of this conversation.
Peter, what
did you do?
He was slightly inconveniencing
me and Joe,
so we threatened
to destroy his family.
What?
I know, right?! It's pretty galling.
No, I'm not taking
your side, Peter!
Whatever the
hell you did,
you go find him
and bring him back!
All right,
I'll go find him.
God, I'm sorry.
You're makin' me feel lower
than a squid at
the bottom of the ocean.
Wow, it really inks in here.
What is that?
There you are.
Listen up, Meg:
this TSA isn't sweaty
enough for the two of us.
What?
What does that even mean?
It means, stay away
from Larry.
I'm his girlfriend.
You are?
Oh, my God, I thought
you were a boy.
Oh, that's it!
I will cut you, bitch.
Ow!
That hurt a little bit.
This ain't over.
Larry is mine.
What the hell?
Th-That was crazy!
Like-like crazier
than putting cops on Segways.
Help, officer!
There's a lady being
raped in that alley!
Okay, hold on, let me do
a small dippy-bob turn.
I couldn't
be sure,
but I-I think the
man has a knife!
Are there any steps
leading to that alley
or is it just a series
of gentle ramps?
Okay, guys, Lois wants me
to find Cleveland.
And since he eats, like,
nine candy bars a day,
if we wait here
at the convenience store,
he's bound
to show up.
Hey, can you buy
us some beer?
I don't know, I don't
think it'd be right.
Ugh, I knew you weren't cool.
Well, now, now,
hold on a minute...
See? This is
pretty cool, huh?
Yeah, I guess.
But what we could
really use is some weed.
I think that might
be over the line.
See?
I told you this guy wasn't cool.
Well, now, now,
hold on a minute...
Mr. Griffin,
did you or did you not
distribute alcohol
and marijuana to minors?
No, Your Honor,
I did not.
Told you this defendant
wasn't cool.
Well, now, now, now,
hold on a minute...
Still no sign of Cleveland?
Yeah. I was thinking
maybe our best bet
is to just drive
around town
and see if we
can spot him.
Okay, well, he's not at
the mini golf course.
Okay, he's still not at
Oh, wow. Look at
that windmill.
Peter, do you want to go mini golfing?
Yes.
Well, he wasn't
by the sno-cones!
I love today!
Hi, Meg.
Larry, what are
you doing here?
I-I thought we were gonna
meet at the Tumi store
and see who buys
luggage at the airport.
Meg, I've got some
disturbing news.
Some Grey security tubs
have gone missing.
Oh, my God! The ones
we have a zillion of
but are somehow never there
when people need them?
That's right,
and I'm going to have
to check your locker.
I don't need to tell you
how serious this is.
Wait, Larry!
I was framed!
I bet it was Marla!
I'm sorry, Meg,
you're fired.
I'm going to need
your small, ridiculous tie.
You're firing me?
I have a duty
to this country.
And with people
like you stealing tubs,
how are we ever going
to catch Abu Nazir?
That's not even
a real person.
That's the terrorist
from Homeland.
And they caught him.
Good-bye, Meg.
Good-bye, Larry.
Meg?
I'll miss the way you reminded
people about their belts.
We've looked everywhere.
Where the hell could he be?
Guys, I think we need to
embrace the possibility
that Cleveland
never existed.
Dammit, if only there was
some kind of clue
as to where
he might be.
That's right,
Cleveland had a deli!
We should
check there!
Cleveland!
Oh, sweet! Egg salad!
Peter, this place has been
closed for six years.
So what?
Egg salad don't go bad.
Son of a whore!
Give me some milk!
Okay, that helped.
Jeez, this place is a dump.
Yeah, it is, isn't it?
It's a symbol
of all my failures.
Cleveland!
You're okay!
I'm so glad
we found you!
Hey, listen, I'm sorry
we threatened to blab
about your bachelor
party stripper stuff.
I'd never do that.
'Cause that'd mean I'd
have to talk to Donna,
and that's... that's
just, like, "ugh."
And I'm sorry I caused such
problems in your marriage.
Truth is, I was faking it
as a therapist.
I've been back almost a year
and I still got
nothing going on.
Hey, cheer up,
Cleveland.
What are you
talking about?
I'm a cop.
Oh. W-Wait, that's real?
I thought that was, like,
a Make-A-Wish thing.
All right, come on, buddy.
Let's get out of here.
And, you know,
even though
therapy might not
be your thing,
you've got a job.
As my fourth
best friend.
After the dog?
After the dog.
Peter, thanks for going
to find Cleveland
and bringing
him home safely.
Hey, that's what
friends are for.
Hey, what about you, Meg?
What'd you do this week?
What, so you can
make fun of me?
No, Meg.
I'm your father,
and I'm interested in what
my daughter did this week.
You promise you're not
gonna make fun of me?
Of course, Meg.
I care about my family.
But I-I feel like
you're drawing this out,
so when you do make fun of me,
it'll hurt more.
What? Well,
that hurts, Meg.
You know, you can
be very hurtful.
I'm asking you,
please--
and-and you don't
have to tell me,
I want to know because
I'm interested--
what you did
this week.
It enhances my life to
know how yours is going.
You promise?
Okay, well, now you
owe me an apology.
I'm sorry.
I'm not used to you
wanting to know...
Of course, I'd love
to tell you what happened.
Then by all means.
I-- It's just upsetting
when you thumb your
nose at the family.
But I love you, and
I'm looking forward
to hearing what
you have to say.
Please.
I'd like to hear.
Oh. Okay.
Well, this is
actually kind of funny.
I joined the TSA...
End of the show!
♪ Nah nah nah nah Family Guy,
nah nah start the credits ♪
♪ Lots of little names,
nyah nyah nyah nyah guy! ♪
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru